dressilyme.com 2009-06-21

# Privacy Policy – Myeglobal – Trade With China Suppliers!

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We will never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances, we will work to protect the security and privacy of your any personal information will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy. During your use of this Site, you must abide by our Privacy Policy below. 

#### 1.Information Collection

You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing your any personal information. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with your personal information, you should consent to the transfer and storage of your information to our servers. 

#### 1.1 Personal Information:

  * Email address, physical contact information, and financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers.
  * Your transactional information on Myeglobal. (Such as buying, selling, contents of the items and shop profile that relates to your account).
  * Shipping, billing and other information related to your purchase or shipment of the items.

#### 1.2 Publishing Information:

Your any submitted information is published by the publishing tools on MyeGlobal.com. Including but not only limited to Personal profile, products, Trade Leads and any forum, all these are based on you must consent to the publication of such information. 

#### 1.3 Statistical Information:

We gather statistical information on Myeglobal and our users, such as IP address, browser software, operating system, pages viewed by the unique visitors and so on. 

#### 2.Use of Your Information

#### 2.1 Collected Information

We use the collected information to improve our marketing and promotional strategy, to analyze the site usage, to update our content and product offerings and to customize our site’s service, to improve the layout and service specifically for you. We may use our collected Information to serve your account, including but not only limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential users. We may use your collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message. 

#### 2.2 Personal Information:

We may use your Personal Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which MyeGlobal.com determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Personal Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. 

#### 2.3 Publishing information:

All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on Myeglobal and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to MyeGlobal.com becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not only limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should be cautious when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information you submit to us. 

#### 2.4 Statistical Information:

We use Statistical Information to help diagnose problems and maintain our computer servers, to manage our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Statistical Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. We may provide Statistical Information to third parties, we will never provide personally-identifying information without your permission. 

#### 3\. Disclosure of Your Information

We may share your information with our agents, representatives, service providers, and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer orders, offering certain products and services, enhancing and improving clients’ purchase experience, enabling access to our partners’ web sites, providing a personalized purchase experience, preventing fraud and completing payment method processing. 

We reserve the right to disclose your information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of myeglobal.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

We also reserve the right to disclose your information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority. 

We have reason to believe that a user is in breach of the terms of user agreement or any other agreement on Myeglobal, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such user’s Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to Myeglobal or others. 

#### 4.Using Information from MyeGlobal

Our site enables you to share other user’s personal and financial information in order to complete transactions. We advise you to disclose your privacy information and respect the privacy of other users. We try our best to validate the truthfulness of all users’ submitted information, but we still recommend you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of your trading partner before entering into a transaction. In order to protect your privacy, we allow only limited access to other users’ contact, shipping and financial information to facilitate your transactions. When users are involved in a transaction, they may have access to each other’s name, User ID, email address, and other contact and shipping information. In all cases, you must give other users a chance to remove themselves from your database and to review what information you have collected about them. 

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) to store specific information about you and track your visits to our site. It is very common for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A cookie will be sent to your computer’s hard drive only if you access our site using the computer. If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, you each time usage of the same computer to access our Site, then our web servers will be notified of your usage. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your personal Information and/or publishing Information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by users; research visiting patterns and help target advertisements based on user interests; and track progress and participation in promotions. 

You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser’s which is installed in the computer you are using to access the site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies. If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you may be required to re-enter your information on our site more often and certain features of our site may be unavailable. 

The site and its content are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information. 

#### 7.Change Your Information

You can access, view and edit your registered information, Publishing Information and payment Information (if any) through your Account on MyeGlobal.com, to update or correct such information, please [Click Here](http://www.myeglobal.com/Secure/Logon.aspx)

If you want to unsubscribe to our email communications and details of your company profile please mail to service@myeglobal.com or try contact us

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, and to maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. 

As a registered User, your registration Information, publishing Information and payment information (if any) can be viewed and edited, that just need to enter your account with you ID number and your password.   
We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.   
Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and password) on the computer.   
Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished the on line activities. 

No data transmission over the Internet.   
As a result, although we try to protect your information, there is not a web site or company, including Myeglobal can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information, what you transmit or undergoing will be at your own risk. 

#### 9.Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes of the Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posted an amended and restated privacy policy on our site. Our posting the amended and restated privacy policy will make such new privacy policy immediately effective. You agree that all personal information collected will be governed by the newest privacy policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our privacy policy, you should contact MyeGlobal.com in writing and specifically request that MyeGlobal.com return and/or all copies of all or part of your collected information in MyeGlobal.com's possession. This privacy policy was last amended on August 10, 2007.
